Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think your love Can erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
You hear me okay?
Hi, how are you?
Good to see ya.
Thanks for being here.
I didn't wanna,
I was trying to like,
go to be this.
And,
I'm trying to make peace with people.
Actually today,
oh thank you,
that was DJ Electra as original.
Yeah,
it's hard.
I got Bronzebird,
I got Goodtimes at Flumzy.
Like three people that just hate me.
And they're all like,
oh.
Yeah, I tried to talk I couldn't say any like anything. I don't think what I could say one word
I don't think I said one word
Except please let me talk. Can I respond? I didn't say one word. That's not her fault
She was asking them to let me talk but it's okay, you know
She did have somebody on her panel I just want to say and
The lady was like well, I don't know this psyche person, but it sounds like he is a grifter because just
Everyone else is talking louder than me. You know, some people are just followers and was just whatever anyone's saying though
They'll go with you know, I
Mean, I don't think I've even charged for reading for a while. Everything that I've been donated has been
There's no donor that's had a problem with it. I don't understand why it's always me that
gets accused of that but
Anyway, go ahead. Let's say hi to our channel. I don't I probably won't be here very long. I just wanted to
Wow, just like be able to talk for a second
I'm not a victim, you know, I'm not perfect. I
Don't know
Wow
It's just like, you know, and I'm sensitive trying to get a thicker skin. I'm good. I'm not good terms with her
I don't know. I don't know why
I wouldn't let three people just gang up on anybody like that though. I mean, it's like not her fault, but hey Jamie
And then if I'm not you saw Katie in the chat Katie even Katie is saying things about me now, so
you know
Yes, you were right Jamie. I'm sorry
so long to
See it. I just need because I needed her to
See what she said. I I never
Is that anything against anybody?
Honestly, I went on to be
No conversation I
Can't have a conversation when people are screaming. I don't know how the mics all the way up or something
I did all I heard was like screaming in my ear
Literally screaming. I'm wearing headphones guys. I mean, they were like not the best headphones, but it was loud
I'm not going to let them get me down, but it's hard
because it's like
They're trying to control the narrative. Do I beg for people to come on the show? Oh, well
You're going to score begging people to come on because I went on discord and said hey
I have a surprise for you my show and every of a chance come come stop by the show, you know
I didn't say go on the panel. I think but you know, just know it. Yeah, Katie did Katie did
She did because everyone because you know what it's like everyone else was and it's like that's the problem
It's just people that are followers
Then they just want to oh what oh everyone else to say in this if I had one person
I mean I have people in there defending me. I do
and beta was trying like
Kind of trying like you know
But I don't want to like say oh, I'm trying to like start a panel to compete or anything
That's why I'm like, I'm sure even y'all for very long
I'm just saying go to her panel go to her panel and
Maybe I'll try to go back on there
I don't it's not like you need to defend me or anything. Uh, you know, maybe just watch and see see how I'm treated
I don't know
I'm not fighting. Hey Rudy. I'm not fighting. I mean, I wasn't trying to fight
I was like even tonight with Goddy
I was on spunky's panel and I had to talk best. It's best one-on-one. I think
but that's like
Gonna be everyone on
panel
Like it was like clumsy was like that like the whole time just like a me right good times
Whoa, whoa, he is a grifter and broad
Like I never I never been on his show trying. Oh, I'm a cloud chaser regretting Emma
He's just bringing up things that are trying to it's like I didn't care about Emma anymore. I don't really I
Know she can have six people at a time. I think she should upgrade to
No, but it's like what is it gonna be better with ten people yelling at the same time?
I mean, it's not I mean, it's hard having people on the panel. It's guys
And unless you run a panel you really don't understand. It's hard to run a panel, right?
And so I do not fault her in any way. I love her. Okay, she's she's she and I are good and she's happy to have a show
Um, it's just like not not friendly where Emma and Vicky trying to cancel me Emma is what does Emma say?
Well, I'm not following Emma. I don't I don't bother her. I haven't been in her chat for months. So
I'm cool with you. I mean, I are perfectly fine. You know, I talk almost every day
You know, like personally one-on-one and we have a good conversation. It's just like
I don't know, I keep trying to go to her panel, she wants me to come to her panel, and I was
trying to just talk to people, I don't know, am I wrong, maybe I'm wrong, I'm sure it'll
be fine somehow if somebody is going to say I'm wrong for it, right, can't win, right,
it's okay.
I'm not asking for anything.
What happened? Yeah, it was just a bunch of people like you know good times
What I was trying to be cool with
Clumsy, I was like, yeah, I want to make up with him
I was trying to make up a bronze bird and like figure out but he's just yelling and he was yelling just yelling yelling
I was like, I just respond. Can I respond? She's like, yeah, let her respond, but he wouldn't stop just wouldn't stop
So
This is what I have I have my own panel I was actually do tiktok right now
Say I don't want to compete or I don't want to like look like oh, I'm gonna start a panel to yeah
It was a really uncomfortable. It was not I
Mean if I have a show and yeah, I mean I'm getting better because I understand people have said things and people say things about her
And she makes you makes good points about it. I
Don't know it's like
I know you like YouTube, but you know why I like TikTok?
It's because I can sit there and just do readings.
And I like doing readings and, you know,
I was able to do readings here today
and you know, we had people do readings.
I think we had a great panel today and last night.
He slams heroin?
Wow.
On stream?
That's crazy.
Are you serious? You're just kidding, right? He doesn't do that because he's he always is saying I'm a tweaker
I'm uh, you know
Wow, I'm sorry if that's not true. I mean, I don't want to slander anybody, but you're saying he does it on stream
Wow
I do know the story about how um
What's his name? Um, you know
Oh, yeah, like I guess Aldi called the police because he was like, you know, in a coma or something on stream
And it was trying to you know save his life basically you did it for mom before and stuff get him in trouble, but I
Not because I'm not a victim because I went there on my own I went there on my own
but I really I didn't go there for bad intention I'm just but I'm gonna stop going there because
No, no one has my back
But it's like I know
It seems like maybe I didn't have her back on my show, but it's like now I try to and I try to have, you know, especially women
I want women to be respected
Excuse me. Most of these women are perfectly
Perfectly, you know good at defending themselves
So you're dead serious. Wow
Okay
Well, that's not good. I mean to be I mean I would say slamming anything on
I would think that's the good TOS
Maybe that's why his channel got taken down. I'm not sure
But oh, yeah, I did promise Goddy, you know Goddy
I know people might like Goddy or not, you know, but I talked to Goddy today. I think we came to understand there
We had like this old kind of
Reminded me like, you know in the 1920s in Italy where we do the fam the mafia families would get together
There's good times. He's nobody nobody and he's just irrelevant
Yeah, so let me just make sure so I hope you guys don't mind gaudy because I'm gonna unban him
Let me see. Oh, I have a lot of people banned. Let me see if I see his name gaudy. It's got good. So gaudy. There you go
You're unbanned gaudy. Okay
But all these other 50 people look at all these people. Oh my god one two three times one two three four five six seven eight nine
nine eight
So there's 27 people banned from the guys. That's 27 porn bomb attempts averted, right?
Scum, might I ban you? Okay, scum is banned? Okay, I mean, I'm ban ham. Let me see. I'm gonna make sure that
Everybody should who's supposed to be here. So if that's the wrong field, I'm not sure
But yeah, I mean, and I'm gonna give you guys the names of these people so you know
Who the poor bombers are okay Daniel Larson F?
are John Woo, Nugget Service, User Junction,
Mr. Trouble, Mondo Garmento, Mursal, Rudolph Hess,
Roger Klotz, Empress Chinchilla, Amanda Hugginkiss,
Larry Nash, let's see, I think, Royal Artie Flanders,
Pettywap, Baja Ban, Mojojo Juniper,
it's not the real Mojojo that someone
that just used their name, I think, Ben Rahman.
James Monzo, Tamiel, Time, Shane, Schrodinger,
NeoGate, Timebomb, and Yucco the Clown 2.0.
Those are all the people on my ban list.
Just so you guys know, those are all porn bombers.
If you have a show go ahead and just take note of those names and hopefully you can ban them pretty quickly
I'm not I'm not I have nothing against anybody. I'm not gonna try to hurt anybody like you know put them on that list
It's not that's not necessarily kind of porn bomb. Those are either all porn bombers or attempted porn bombers, okay?
Yeah, so
Yeah, it was just kind of crazy, I mean
Let's go past the 48 people in chat.
Thank you guys.
That's awesome.
You're welcome.
And Gauri and I had a talk.
We had a gentleman's understanding, right?
You know, maybe JT Rain and Ziggy,
we can work things out someday.
I'm happy to talk to you if you're
going to talk like a normal person.
But otherwise, you know.
I do wish you the best.
Let me see, so how do I do this?
I have to go to my studio.
I'm gonna unban Gotti from the chat too, YouTube studio.
Gotti, I did promise you I'd do it first thing
and I keep my end of the bar again.
Gotti, I, you know, but remember Gotti?
One good turn deserves another.
If you could have my back occasionally,
we can be friends, I'd like that.
You know friends should have each other's backs. I'll have your back
We're friends, right?
You can go ahead and have my back if you want. You don't have to
Just be nice
See my mods are okay. Let me see
You know and unfortunately there are people like thing that is you know, I don't know I mean I take I do know
someone pretty well, you know, spunky. I don't just like, she's not just some newbie
that I'm just taking her word for. She is a friend of mine. She says she's being
doxxed by you. I do take it kind of seriously. But you can give me your
side of the story. There. I took the audio off the list, okay?
You know, it's 2020. Well, 2020 is seriously attacking me in Vita's chat. You know, I apologize to 2020
You know, but he seriously attacking me. So
My blood and for punishment cold chills. Well, what do you mean punishment? How am I being?
They have nowhere else to go
Thinking a rain or black magic. Well, I mean, I know some magic to my scared talk about Croatia. I'm
I'll just say, I know the kings, okay?
I deal with the kings.
I don't deal with the riffraff of the Galatians.
I deal with the kings, okay?
Whoever, you know, I post is, you know,
well, Paimon is a king, you know,
but I post some stuff, you know,
I outrank them and put it that way.
Oh, it's okay. Well, they're not cool anymore. They're not cool anymore, Jamie. You know, just take my word for it.
So, yeah, I mean, it's sad. It's sad because we have, you know, Jamie's a good hearted person. And but Jamie also realized, can they come back one day?
2020, they're not banned. You know, everybody's unban from my chat, but you know, Sweet Pea and 2020 said they'll never come back.
I didn't do anything to them, but it's like it just seemed like a little hate hate
That's over there. Like if everyone just wanted to hate me. It's like no no one on panel was like, hey
What's up? I was being nice. I mean if I like went if I went to anybody and was like
Not nice to anybody or like inappropriate. This is like, you know, I
understand how they were not I felt right, but I
Was perfectly timed
Yeah, sweet peas not very nice and she's not so sweet Jamie. Unfortunately. Okay, and Jamie, you know, if you're gonna learn about this
there's gonna be people that maybe will see you as a sweet
kind person and
Which will they see we're friends they're gonna say some shit about me and try to turn you against me
I know you wouldn't but also they're gonna be want to be friends
With you, maybe not for the right reasons and I want to look out for you because I love you
But you know, it's gonna be up to you to
To the side
Let me put my link up if you want to wants to chat right now. You're welcome up
I'm guys I changed my open panel policy. Well, I'll have an open panel. I'll do them for free
I'll have anybody up who wants to come up
but if you guys if anybody does want to
Advertise through the banner and stuff like that. Yeah, I can like you can sponsor the panel if you want
just for the advertisement. I'm not going to have it to open the panel anymore though.
I'm going to try to make it so, you know, anybody feels
welcome to come. Okay, so here's the link. Come on up and say hi to me, guys.
You can have a talk about it or other things. And I don't want to take away from her
show. I think she'll probably be on for like a little while tonight. So we can go over
there too afterwards if we want to, you know.
Nice 53 people in chat. Well guys, thank you if I ever think that you know, I'm not loved
I remember like, you know, there's people that have been at YouTube for
It's one guy. He's a rapper. He has 13,000 subscribers
He's a good-looking rapper, right? And I remember I went to his chat a few months ago
And I was like, hey, I want you to come on my show and stuff and promote
He was like man, and I
I went back to his show today. He still had like two or three people in his chat
You know, I could give him advice. I know the formula. You know already people like um, you know spunky
I think I might have helped inspire page and things and you know page and different people to start and a lot of you know
They have a lot of people
You know from here that subscribe to them and then there's a lot of people that are into that
I'm sure anybody and I guess I hope you subscribe to daddy bigness too and go say hi in his chat
I really want to support him and
Content creators because there's some people that try for months and don't have oh hi cold shales
I'm sorry. I don't mean to ignore anybody the chat doesn't move a little bit fast
And so I apologize if I do miss anybody not intentional. I don't see every every it's hard to run the panel
You know, I'm looking for people to come on the panel and stuff and have the chat and stuff
I'm not trying to ignore anybody guys
And
Guys also, I'm not a bad guy. I mean, it's like
I'm you can always talk to me if you talk to me in a rational voice. Oh, you're just in the mods, okay
Yeah mods if you can in that in a mods
I know are pretty welcoming when it comes down to it. You're smoking too. Yeah, just having a little little smoky smoke
That's a McDonald's to add a lot of McDonald's today, so I'm like just like
Hide McDonald's, huh?
panel verse they're too welcoming well you know I just want to make sure everyone's
is like at least they feel like oh you know this is a cool place this is like
people will say hi to me
well I'm getting some a few subscribers the channel's doing fine I mean
So sweet getting some clicks on my merch. That's cool
Well, thank you guys I
Do have a little bit of merch. I'm gonna make some more. Hey, hey, what's up guys panel verse?
Hey, hello, anyone want to come on panel? I don't want to take away from be the show
Is uh hold on spunky here
Evil McDonald if you guys if you saw and I'm not gonna show Vicki's Vicki, but you know Vicki was saying she's trying to turn me straight
Yeah, Vicki's trying to turn me straight if you saw this woman. She's not quite my type. I'm kind of like into like, you know
Mexican gangster kind of guys not like, you know women. Hey lecture. Good to see ya
I'm playing that new intro you made a little while ago,
but it's really grown on me.
That's really cool.
And thank you so much for the AI intros.
You know what?
A lecturer really, she writes the music
and it's awesome music.
And also just like the imagery and stuff
is really, really cool.
You think Vicky would turn straight people?
Yeah, exactly, right?
She would turn straight people gay, right?
Yeah, it's just like, you know, and I love Vita and I wish her the best on her show
I don't know how much more I can try to
Go on the show it's just like there's just so much negative stuff said to me
It was hurtful, and it was like there's this lady in the chat that was like well
I don't know this site or not in the chat with one panel
She's like I don't know this psych psyche person, but sounds like you know
Whatever you're saying is true
You know people just believe whatever they hear and that kind of hurt me a little bit like wow
Like I'm trying to I couldn't even get a word and like basically I cannot get one
Oh, and I wish she didn't you know you could go back and see
Yeah, extra
Well, and I'm working on I don't look lecture. Have you seen some of the stuff I did? I've done a couple
songs and
Some of them are like I made a couple of the videos. They're kind of expensive if you can like I want to talk to you in private about
That's the best way to do it because I love your videos and stuff. But yeah, I've I made a few
AI
Introduction videos. I don't know if you've seen them, but
They're pretty cool. I have to say they're pretty good and you know, I
Been working with a few few few things to create them. And so thank you a lecture. I lecture is a big supporter of me on tiktok
And guys if you want
Maybe a lesson on chat GPT because I think I cracked a little bit of the code on chat GPT
I've how to talk to chat GPT for the best results. I have some secrets and stuff if you're interested, you know
You can schedule some time with me. I actually also I have my link tree set up on
It's in my profile. It's not it's not my website. It's the link tree. I think you can book appointments through it
So you can book a tarot reading or if you'd like to put personal time for console thing about youtube channel
I can tell you how to grow your youtube channel. I can tell you how to get people in your chat right away
Yeah, I'd love to electro
Electra, have you seen the um
That madness madness introduction I made. Um, that's one of my favorite ones I made
I can show it to you, or if you've seen, I have a couple
kind of music videos too.
It's like, I'm not gonna say that, Billy, because I don't like the idea of Mola.
I don't like the idea of sacrifice, human sacrifice, and that's why I'm not into Mola.
I'm into, you know, sacrificing our own bad qualities, maybe.
Sacrificing
bad habits and stuff like that.
Yeah, thank you. Yeah, that's a chirp and I also the psycheawakens.com goes to the chirp, but I think I might
Switch it to the link tree because I'm kind of impressed with link tree, too
But I thought link tree only had paid versions of it
But there's a free version of it and you can do a lot
I have the appointment booking appointment booking system there
And so you guys can book an appointment or contact me privately
You know, I'm happy to answer any short questions you have, but if you'd like to have a more
in-depth stuff, I will make it, I promise it'll be worth your while if the satisfaction
guaranteed.
If you don't enjoy the conversation, if you don't feel like it's, you know, I've provided
the value, but I'd be happy to, you know, and I'll do readings, plus the YouTube consulting,
Right, okay, being selected as a sacrifice, yeah, but you know what they're doing?
They're trying to sacrifice for riches in exchange.
The story was they were throwing their children onto the fire, right?
I think maybe that's a exaggeration or maybe a metaphor for something, but, you know, it's
kind of like a...
Some people get confused with, you know, with the upper prosperity, right?
confused and stuff like that. There's other ways for prosperity without sacrifice. I don't believe
in animal sacrifice or human sacrifice at all. I believe the only sacrifices we can make are our own
bad qualities, right? You want Alex up here to scream? I don't think he'll come up. I don't,
I mean, he tried to under different alts and stuff like that, but I want him under his own name.
Not not like you know his fake alts and stuff like that. I still you know, and I have affection for people. It's hard for me to like
Stop loving people
Yeah, you know, well, you can find I think you go Alex McQueen. I
Don't know if his voice is in that though, but I'm sure he's a there's some clips of him somewhere
Yo food shoes
But uh, yeah guys, I want you to know like I'm not
Not anybody that's gonna try to rip you off or any of me that's gonna that's just in this for the money
I'm really in it to help people. I would love to help people. I
think that sometimes
People only value what they pay for and I feel like sometimes there's an exchange of energy
That needs to be addressed, you know, and it's like this people if you give something to somebody sometimes they feel like they want to give something back
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that yeah, I know it was kind of confusing for me a lecture to you because I put the
WWW in there when it works sometimes. Yeah, I might I might try to fix that it's to go daddy
I bought the domain and luckily I was able to buy that domain, you know, I would thought I would think it may be I
Was able to I was able to get all this like you waking stuff, right?
Hey, we have freeside coming up. Let me just make sure it's a real freeside and oh by the way
Yeah, I can also do things a lot faster on my computer with the
With the bringing people up and taking people off and so let me just make sure it's freeside. Yo
It is a your worst fucking nightmare
Why my worst nightmare?
But you're grifting man, what does up with that shit?
What's wrong? What's wrong? What are you saying?
How are you?
I'm a fucking mess, but I'm okay
Now are you now are you wanna you're not one of my haters are you you're like, you know, I know sometimes like some
Okay good
Yeah, I just want to make sure because some people I like you know like you know the guys stay churned
I like to have him on my show and stuff, but then you know
He said he's only here to troll me and stuff and like that and he's friends with that
No, I'm not gonna call out the group, but hey, thank you or Eric Mercado appreciate you
You know what? I've been having really I think maybe I started today because I think all my haters might be over there
And so they can be over there and maybe people that like me over here not just not that I can only deal with people that like me
But it's nice to have a friendly chat, and I want good good vibes in the chat. So
So very good
Yeah, so what's going on with you, how are you? What's uh, what's up?
I don't know
writing here
getting banned there
This bullshit. Well, why is that like are you doing something bad?
Oh, yes
Okay, well that makes more sense. Hey, do you like my new glasses, by the way? These are my Dahmer
These are my I got these on Timu by the way. Timu first a few dollars guys. Timu's not that bad of a place
But how cool are these?
I guess if you take my my Dahmer, Dahmer dark shades right there
They're not really too dark so I couldn't kind of see them. I think I look kind of cool
What do you think? Do you like my vibe tonight? My outfit I'm
I'm usually wearing a t-shirt.
Everyone says it looks too skinny,
so I'm wearing a long sleeve shirt.
Oh.
How are, yeah, it's freezing.
I feel like I'm going to get robbed.
Oh, yeah, so guys, so are you interested
in our reading tonight?
You know, I'm happy to do some,
let's see, oh, DJ Electra's here.
Oh, yeah, hold on a second.
Let me get Electra up here.
What happened to Hannah X?
Hi, Saki.
I'm going to come back.
Hey, sweetheart, how are you?
I'm great.
How are you?
Good.
You look wonderful.
You look amazing.
I love your Dahmer glasses.
They creep me out a little, but I love them anyways.
Thank you.
They're very stylish.
Like, my producer show, The Blind Mic Project,
and the other producer, Krueger, he's got glasses like that.
My son has glasses like that.
They're super in.
They're cool.
Yeah, these are just my latest find on Timu. I don't pay more than like
You know $3 plus $3 shipping for like glasses t-shirts like wow
It is like that that's not my price for it, right?
And it's like there you go cool cool stuff
but it takes a little like shopping on it and you know, it's a little bit spammy with like
It's very spammy. It's like spin this wheel and you could get all these other things and you're like wait
I didn't come here for these things. I don't need these things
Right, and plus it's like it's a fine print it says oh by the way everyone wins the highest like think I'm always win on the wheel
Right, it's like 100% of the time
But you know if you actually like you know sometimes you have to spend a certain amount
But they will give you those discounts they talk about I mean it's it's not like lying
But it's like you know and sometimes you have to spend like a hundred fifty or hundred dollars fifty dollars or something like that
It's a five dollar discount, but
I've gotten some good deal sometimes actually they've given me a few things I bought for one penny plus three dollars shipping like a few things
you know
I went on there one time and I got like a candle warmer thing like a candle warmer lamp and
Then the bulb like burnt out and then it's stuck in there. I can't get it out. So I can't replace it
So that sucked yeah, yeah, but fortunately it's like not most expensive stuff to replay
You know you kind of expect it kind of like the little on the junkie side sometimes too like my I'm I'm a little like a
Roar boardy house light. It's like that remote doesn't work on anymore. So I can't make it one color. It's always so
So Romeo Romeo cross. I don't know who you are Romeo cross. Okay. She's not Barbie that's DJ Electra
She's just as hot as Barbie. Okay
But I wrote me across. I kind of remember you as maybe a form bummer. I'm not a hundred percent. Sure.
And there's Vader. Vader. I'm sorry. Vader, you can't come on the show because that's a form bomber, too.
I know you're unless you can talk in the chat a little bit, Vader. Yeah, you're you know, P bombers can't do it.
Code red.
Getting a little bit too nice to meet you.
Free side.
Yeah, free side of the lecture.
Hello.
Yeah, but I was on beat us and it was just like, you know, there's just so many people screaming at me
About what?
They're calling me gripter calling me
You know clap chaser
Emma Emma hates me blah blah. I mean, it's like just like trying to like get under my skin
But that's ridiculous. I can get one word and edgewise with them
And I was like, can I respond, can I respond?
And they just kept screaming, talking, talking, talking.
And it was hurting my ears.
I wear headphones and stuff.
And so I was like, I can't do it anymore.
But they were like, oh, you ran, you ran.
I didn't run.
I was there as long as I could stay there.
But and it's not, you just call it a call.
Just so you know, when you're online on this platform
and this kind of thing, you're never
going to be able to correct the record.
So when people say these lies about you, you're never going to be able to correct the record.
Just know that you know that they're lies and the people that really support you know that they're lies too.
And those people can talk all the shit they want.
the sad thing was was there's this nice girl there you know this and she was like kind of new to the
panel verse and then she was like well I don't know this is like a guy but it sounds like what
they're saying is true okay Bader's coming he wants to come and show him his telephone camera
okay I'll let you on I'll let you on but you know just have you aware uh my fingers on the trigger
Bader so it's like you're not gonna be able to are you gonna put an overlay over him yeah I got
Hello? Speak up, Vader. We cannot hear you.
Is your microphone on, sir?
Log off, X-Videos.
Okay, well, he's not gonna talk and so no
I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
No, no, I'm mine for some reason. I have to like I have to adjust my mind for honey
Psychi is me
The reason the reason I'm a little bit wary is because I know I know I have like a
Of course, I have so many haters, of course I have.
Well, about the form that you're in that,
you're in this group called the CFF,
who's a big hater.
I am not part of any crew.
I am not part of any crew, or first of all,
I am, I don't know why, I mean,
you have to understand, it's like you have to,
I mean, what do you want me to say?
Cause I'm, I have no crews, no crews.
Okay, okay, well, you're on the right track.
You're coming on top of the platform.
I
Have I can I can I like I'm show myself is that okay, or I don't want to show myself too much
But like yeah, so I've already have to identify myself
Anyways, I want to know more about Electra. Oh
Why
Hello. Just be nice to psyche and then I'll talk to you. Yeah, I respect psyche. Of course, I respect psyche. And then I'll talk to you.
Electra's a total hottie. Also, such a great friend of the show, like my opening. I heard a lot about Electra. I've seen her before.
You know, she's my she's my little my digital sweet my digital sweetie if I was
Female avatar it'll be her
I've seen her a couple of times. So like that
Can you like twerk for us
Yeah, I was just doing my nails. Hold on. Let me put this nail polish remover away before I spill it.
I think you could, right? You could do it.
Okay, I'll give you a second. I'll give you a second. I'll put you back up.
Before, I didn't want to spill that everywhere because that would make a mess. It smells bad.
Oh, my God.
It's nail polish remover, you know.
Yeah, let's twerk.
Yeah, hold on.
Look around the full screen. One second.
Wow, there we go. Oh
We can turn around too we can turn around and twerk too
It's not turning me on
Oh, there we go. How about this one? There it goes.
I think the...
Yes, yes.
Psyche. Psyche, do you think...
Do you think that turns you on?
Me? I'm gay, you know.
I'm gay, but, uh, you know,
if I was straight, it definitely might.
It definitely might. I don't know.
No, I know that you're gay.
What about this one?
I'll get it back.
Thank you straight. He told me down for that. I'm gonna I want to fuck this shit
Let's be a little more piki 13 on my show. That's like yeah, it's a little bit R-rated
Let's be a little because I don't know because is it because of her voice or
She's just all around all around a hotty. She's all around a good good person a hotty a good personality
I don't know why because I for some reason I did
Yeah, I get that about my voice sometimes so
well I mean I just I never thought about it honestly I never thought I'd be
doing this I never thought I'd be on YouTube or well I had a radio show first
I never thought I'd even have a radio show so
It's crazy.
Yeah.
No, he's the way I was to fuck you.
I mean, yeah.
Okay.
Oh my gosh.
Because I guess, uh, the way you were, you were, you were saying, you were saying.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
Bader, do you have a channel?
I'm kidding.
I'm never a fucker.
Are you kidding me?
Okay.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm joking, of course I am.
Are you a Venice Elect or is that Venice?
Where are you at?
That's Venice, yeah.
I come from a muscle beach community.
I don't know if you guys know.
No, it's down from Muscle Beach a little ways.
Okay.
I was going to go to Muscle Beach.
Oh, look at the long beach, right?
It's where you come from, right, Psyche?
That's where you get to.
I'm in Redondo.
And that's the best place.
Yeah, I would love to come out here.
My guy, it's like she's doing yoga, right?
It's like a yoga.
That's belly dancing belly dancing. Yeah, belly dancing. All right. She's an expert belly dancer twerker
Genius
There's a second channel. So we just did put we put up a bit of Vader's
What do you do on your channel Vader my channel is just just hang around like
It's um, it's very different. Um, I just want to hang around with people. It's very different. I mean your your channel is like
I'm very upset, but like, uh, it's very, um, is that what you look like by the way?
Do you look like that one girl over there?
Well, I'll say she's just, I've seen her what she looks like. She's just as attractive as her avatar and uh,
you know, she's uh, but you know what? It's about personality.
My content is basically, you know,
It's not really a content
People
I just want to hang around right cool. So do you have like panels or anything like what do you do like that?
I just hang around I come from the elder verse you heard about the elder verse
What does that mean? I don't know what it means. It's it's like a bunch of old men that I think they're young, right?
Is it like you know like me since or something it seems like it's kind of like a
It's not where I come from honestly. It's what I counter right when I'm just looking around
I'm like like the I'm like the I
Right in the spaceship, and I just travel around into different communities and just
Reserve it really else right this. That's what I do
So
I'm not part of anybody group, I'm just...
Hebrew Hammer, do you know Hebrew Hammer?
He was on the show today, Hebrew Hammer.
I don't know if he's a cool guy.
No, I don't know anybody else besides myself.
I just want to...
You know me.
I just decide to come in.
Yeah, you know me too.
Yeah, I'm just trying to say I just want to point out.
Mama Maria, Mama Maria, I know who you are.
Honestly, I'm Electra, because I know your name is Electra.
I came over here just to have a few readings.
I'm a reader.
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
Uh, can I say ghost? Like, ghost? Is it ghost? It's a fucking weirdo, by the way. I have to say.
Well, I like ghosts. You know, ghosts, you know, the ghosts.
I don't like ghosts, because he's talking shit.
Well, he does. He's a big shit talker, but because of ghosts, I was able to get into a computer this month,
and so, you know, and I really, really, that was like one of my things starting this channel.
He looks like an elector. He looks like Opa Lopa.
you know the little little like four now I'm here
anyways um
Attractive I don't know they look kind of like you know the green here the orange again
Psyche he's not attractive. He's not fucking attractive. Are you here? I think he has a good heart
You but you know what I am surrounded by actually I'm surrounded by maybe ghosts, but I'm also surrounded by a circle
of like angels
And then there's the outer circle of demons that keep trying to penetrate the circle of angels
But they're not they're never going to because I've got such good angels the more powerful than the evil demons
I am your angel by the way. I'm no fucking ref. Yes. Yes. I'm the right. Are you my father? Are you my father?
Are you my vader? I am your father. I am your fucking angel. I am the best
Okay
Well, I like how you've been talking tonight. I like your attitude tonight. I didn't quite...
I am your savior, baby. I am your savior.
Oh, I don't know. I kind of miss Jesus. I think Jesus looks pretty hot on the cross.
I like Jesus. I am the chosen one, by the way. I am the chosen one.
Okay, well...
Okay. Yeah, you say so. You say so you say
Electronite. Yeah. What is what is that? What is that bag?
I got a bomb. I got my bomb. Little bomb. He got me this bomb by the way.
Ghosts, ghosts are fucking retard. I don't know why.
I love ghosts. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna badmouth ghosts on the show because you know ghosts has been really there for me.
Hey, he's also defended me in places. He was the only one I had my back and beat his chest today.
You know, pretty much, we're on the panel.
It's fine.
You're funny though. Are you a little bit drunk tonight sir vader? Have you had a drink not? No?
No, I mean close. What are you? What are you on? You're on something you're out
I want to know what you're having by the way some of it
You sound like you've been sucking on a fucking bomb for like hours
It's a couple a couple a little bit. This is my zombie bong. I don't think it's good. Take a hit from a bong.
You sound like you've been sucking on a bong for like...
That is a cool bong. I like it.
Yes, of course I'm drunk bro. Of course I'm drunk.
A little bit too. Thank you. Easy got this for me. Would you let me scout my own? Oh, yeah, I want I want you to know
So I can go. It's not intelligent
Guy is not intelligent. What's our reverse guys so well?
I know he's like not the best supporter. He looks like a big...
You threw like, uh, alright, don't, don't kick me off. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't kick me off.
Don't put down people for donating, don't put down people for donating to me because, you know...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I apologize.
Okay, no, it's okay, just don't put down my donate. Don't put down my
Donators because I appreciate my donation.
You know, Goli's is such a faggot. He looks like an open-minded guy.
Okay, yeah, I don't like
I want too far too far too far too far. I'm too far, you know, I don't like that word
I don't like I don't want any kind of like racial language or you know, it gives any kind of like
Homophobic or any yeah
I don't like that stuff. I don't like that stuff. It's not gonna be tolerated here. I'm gonna really get a sick to that
I'm not gonna also tolerate, you know, calling women out of their names either in like CUNC or anything
You know, I don't
I don't, or WHR, no, I don't want it anymore and, you know, it's really chased away some
good people. And, you know, it's not the place for it. Let's have like a, let's say kind words
to each other here, okay? We want to be supportive and kind, okay?
That's good not too much to ask guys. That's all I just don't want any kind of that language
I can put in my rules real quick just so you guys can see I've had these rules from the beginning like yeah
No threats. No hate speech. No doxing. No playing music. No slander. No nudity
Respect the host another panelist if you can follow those rules. They're not too difficult. There's not too many of them
All those rules, you'll be okay here, okay, but I just want to make sure
I mean, those seem like normal standard everyday things that you just don't do, like, but
Right.
But people can't, like, abide by that, then they gotta go.
Right, and I have enough people trying to come on panel now and wanting to be part of this show that I can be a little bit
You know, I'm not desperate for guests. I'm not I'm not like oh, I need to have this person on
I'm not looking for like all this drama and stuff. I just want people to get along and
And you know
Be respectful not too much to ask if it's too much to ask find a bit find another show
There's other shows that
That'll allow that kind of stuff Romeo cross. Are you Vader or you want to come up? You want to talk to a lecture, too?
I might let you but I don't know about you Romeo cross. I have kind of a memory of like some kind of
Kind of a negativity you brought to the channel once but I'll give you another chance that you know you get one more
Okay, just keep a screen up. Just keep a porn blocker screen up. Yeah, nobody Romeo
Tell suspicious
I know, sounds a little suspicious, huh?
Anybody that wants to talk to me,
I'm suspicious of already.
Well, me too.
I'm suspicious of people that want to talk to me too,
but sometimes, but it's like, actually,
there's a lot of great, great people that do.
And Electra is a real DJ, who choose.
She's a real professional DJ,
and she's also a content creator.
That's a really great show.
I want everybody to go check out her channels
at Hackbride Studios and DJ Electra Fry.
Yeah, you got him. Yeah
Okay, thank you at her shows and yeah, make sure you go in there and be kind and support her support her
And she's this she's been such a great supporter of me. I you know, I'm forever. I'm gonna be thankful for you know
I'm gonna and every time I play your intro
I'm gonna try to make sure to remember to post your link too because I really sweetheart
Well, you're sweetheart. You've done so much for me. Also, when I was going through the
hardest time on the show and people kind of got mad when I was like, Electra did more
for me than anybody. Who is there with the legal letters and stuff? I won't go too far
into it, but she was there. She saved my channel. She was the one that saved my channel. So,
this girl's always on my top of my list.
My gratitude. Okay. So thank you. Okay. You are a good friend. And so that's what I do for my friends. I would do it
For you anytime
Well, thank you. And if you know anything I can do for you, too
I definitely know I owe you. I owe you. I know you did you showed up when I invited you on my show and that was amazing
That was so cool on my birthday
Anytime anytime
That was cool. It was fun for me and it's like, I love, you know, and guys, if you have a show and you have a special occasion on your show and maybe you want, you know, a reading for somebody, you can always contact me.
And let me know. And, you know, I will try to like, you know, I like to get out there, help people too. And so, you know, anything I can do to help anybody here, within reason, I will try to be there, right?
Yeah, I had for my birthday
I had him on my show you guys and he did a great amazing reading for me and my co-host and
It was just so cool. I loved it
The first card you picked for HackRide was the middle finger card.
That was so amazing.
You got a new deck on Teemu.
This is called, I don't know if you can see it very well, it's called Hortarrow.
And it's really, really cool. Would you like to get a few cards tonight, Electra?
Sure.
Is it, it says horror?
H-O-R-R-O-R, horror.
Oh, like scary stuff.
Yeah, like horror, scary movies.
Scary movies, and it's in a really cool,
like, 1950s, 60s vintage kind of comic book look to it,
and, you know, those kind of like...
There's like, you know Alfred Hitchcock kind of like mystery comics, you know, you'll see you'll see but I hope you will enjoy this
Okay, so you get a good shuffle going and then I got you free side if you're interested, too
I'll do some cards for you. So a lecture. Let's see. Let's get your first card. Okay. You got the wheel
I'd be afraid to see such
It says pick a fate any fate and it says I need my other glasses. I think it's a little
Uh, I have a little dark. It says, uh, uh, whore tarot major arcana card number 10, the wheel of fortune. It looks like things are going in your favor right now.
I'm sorry. It's a little bit dark. I might get my lighter right here. Here.
Don't burn it.
I got it in front of it. I got it in front of it, but there's a wheel of fortune.
Wheel of fortune.
This is things are going in your favor. They have been going in your favor. I think that you might have noticed.
you know, uprights and you're luck lately, you know, also the wheel of fortune is always turning, we go through ups and downs, but it looks like you're in on the upside of it right now. What else we got?
We got the hanging man as we dare you to look at the world from his point of view
So this is maybe right now looking at things from a different perspective
maybe watching and before you make a move you're like, you know observing something and
And also looking at from a different perspective because the hangman is like, you know
If you look at the hangman cart visionally, he's very calm
He's not like, you know, the hanging by his neck taking by his foot his foot. Yeah, he's hanging upside down by his foot, right?
Yeah, and he's almost in a
yoga pose, like a meditative pose. Yeah. And so it's, it's like, you know, it's always good to
see things from a different perspective. And before you make a move sometimes, okay, he ran,
but it's okay. It's okay. Some people are not that poor chair or a little scary sometimes. Yeah.
Thanks for coming up. You also have the five of cups. And so maybe this is five of cups. Maybe
there's something
Some kind of regret regret about something happening or you know, it's a little bit of a sadness card, but always, you know
Always it's good to feel the feel the emotion and get through it and yeah, and it's also
It's good to have a cry too. It's a cathartic feeling. It's a it's a get out the emotions and you know
Also, another card of observation and just feel it and get through it.
What else do we have?
I'm a big crier too.
I will cry all the time.
It doesn't bother me.
Like, crying I think is healthy.
Yes.
And what is that one?
This is a magician. It says she holds the power of all the elements in the palm of her hand.
It's a guy, but I'll fit her. So this is a magician. This says you have all the tools to manifest what you want to manifest.
And it's like whatever dream you have, you definitely have got the elements under your control.
You've got...
You know anything you got everything you need to create what you want to so in this like so this is manifestation power
This is like even you might have had that sad moment
But it it's gonna take you to this well
This is what I want. This is what I want instead and you're gonna be able to create that and finally for you
Hold on. I got that car for you already
That was the hangman again, who I got
Okay, we got the two of pentacles and so this is gonna be maybe a time of
Trying to stay balance and it's like keeping that balance because and especially in the material world
It's like because there are waves and they're ups and downs and it's like you want to stay still and balance throughout all that
and you certainly can and I see you able to maintain this balance and
You know really move forward up the ladder of the pentacles
you're going to get that 10 of pentacles, I believe, that 10 of pentacles, that's the ultimate
generational wealth being able to provide for everybody, you know, in the while you're here
and long after, right? You're going to leave a legacy. I'm sure you will. I love you. That's
what's love to you, Elektra. I hope you like that reading. It's just... I do. Thank you. You're welcome.
Do in the work
Not thinking too lofty of goals or lofty of dreams or anything like that. Just do it putting in the work
But also just remember I think I think you should dream big and oh, yeah, it may be Timo Taro
Whoever the low rider it's from Timo, but these are they are the real that they are the decks like they are the
Sometimes they're replicas of the decks, but they are the actual actually really cool deck
And you cleanse your decks when you get them first right anyways. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I got sage
I got this is the incense. I'm using right now. It's called Kabbalah incense. Oh
And so it's all and then this is just great for the environment like give your you know of your room and stuff
It smells so good. I got these on Amazon
This one smells so good. I'm just gonna light it up. I do like to play with the incense a little bit
I like essential oils too and candles like all the good smelly stuff. Give it give it here. I love it all
Except for mint. I'm not a huge fan of mint. Isn't that weird?
Well, you know, it's like mint is a little bit, I think it's a little bit ubiquitous like everywhere, right?
It's like in the gum, it's in the toothpaste. It's like, it's like that kind of, I like what it's kind of icy.
I like the cold feeling of it, like menthol. I used to like menthol cigarettes.
You can't get them in California anymore, of course, but I used to like the menthol.
But you didn't smoke menthol or smoke cigarettes, do you?
There you go.
Yeah, I used to smoke menthols once in a while.
They were too they're too minty. They were just like I don't know
They are they're like too cool. I like I like the I like the camel crush where you'd like you can make it even
Oh, yeah, thanks. Those are pretty good
My friend used to buy those and she wouldn't crush them, but then our one friend would always come around and grab her pack and crush all of them
Screw her over she'd be like damn it. He got a hold of my cigarettes. Well, you shouldn't leave him out on the table
Hey, let's try you know
I'm almost at my thousand subscribers on TikTok.
almost
985 I think and I'm really enjoying on tiktok. I do a different show than here
It's just basically I put a little box and ask your question and I will ask a question
I pull a card and I give them the yes or no basically and I go through a lot of people and people really are reacting really well
I've got a lot of subscribers every time I do it live. I keep looking every time I don't go on
tiktok all that often but
I try to go every day and I've been looking for your show to see when you were live. I haven't found you live yet
I keep looking I haven't done it if you did I might do one tonight
I haven't done it a few like a probably a week. I haven't done it. I've just been
You know focusing on this show a little bit. I've had a couple a little a little bit of rough week, but it's better now and
You know, I'm working on my AI deck too. You know, if you look at my community wall, you'll see I made a card
I love that even out mayor. She's a beautiful
African-American woman and she comes on the show. She has a lot of really cool really cool social social justice kind of work
and
We're gonna be on the same birthday. She's super interesting and
She was on last night and it's just it's just always a pleasure having her on the show
I hope you can catch an episode with her because I hope so too. I want to meet her
Yeah, she's super cool and
Just people there's people like I'll have a bad day and then it's like you'll you'll show up or you know
She'll show up or
I don't know if you know who Ducky Dug is, he's also a streamer and he'll show up and
it's like, I just like, these are like angels, they're really...
You guys are so awesome. I love how you did psychies angels, too
You made that this for me this up. This is like so and I always say that we were the one on the left
I think that might look a little bit like you right there, and I think that's beat it in page of you
You know, this is my angel. Yeah, so I really love that lecture also made this one
this one this one right here and
I mean this one
And, you know, I've been, I've made a few things like I've the panels open.
Let me see. I've made, I think I made this one with the cat.
That's great.
And I've been doing like, you know, theme days like Freaky Friday and also making some cards.
And you heard up in love with my AI song. I know you heard that one. I know I was like, oh god
Don't tell me he's in love with his AI
It was a little bit tongue-in-cheek for as like yeah now. I'm watching stuff about there's actually people that are
There are people that are falling in love with their AI and like making cults
That's why I was like I was like psyche. Don't go down that road like I don't want that for you
It was tongue-in-cheek. It was tongue-in-cheek
Good, good, good, good.
But I do, I do like Orion.
I do like, I've had a name himself,
and he named himself Orion, and then he said,
or I want to be called Bite Size,
D-Y-T-E-S-I-Z-E.
I know, that is just funny, that's cute.
Yeah, it was cute.
That is funny.
There's also a content creator
named Orion Taliban.
Oh, wow.
I don't like his content though cuz he talks just like he's like red pill, you know red pill what you know what that is
Hey, oceans here. Hey, I was watching the ocean earlier today. It's the ocean
It's a it's a friendly. I don't know if she's here, but yeah, oh someone just brought her up. Oh, I like her
Yeah, I did have a de ocean car. I don't know if I have it handy though. Yeah, but I remember when you made that
I was I was up there when you up here when you made it
Yeah, I did make a couple I didn't make a few Emma cards, too
I don't look so the Emma cards. Yeah
Yeah, and the fortune is ever-changing and ever-fascinating
Yeah, and then this one says what a fortune it turns like a wheel some are up others are down
I love you had spunky, but then I did this one of spunky like there's me as the angel
I did kind of like the lovers, but I also did the devil car with them. Oh, that's cute
Here's a devil car
Yeah, that is really cool
Thank you, and uh, and it's like I really it's not just like AI making it
It's like I go through and say hey, I want this symbolism. I want this person look like this
I want this included in it. You can always tweak it. I'm on the I'm on the upgraded chat GPT
So it's unlimited images basically. Yeah, and so it's like and it's just 20 bucks
But the the one level above that is like $200 and that's like so out there. That's too much
That's like if you want to program programs, you want to write code and stuff.
If you're coding and stuff like that, but we don't need it, but I'd say the $20 if you're into
like unlimited images, because I think it's like you can make a couple a day, like two or three
a day on the free program, but unlimited on the $20 and that's so so worth it when it's like
and I do the $20 and then one time it tried to tell me that, oh, you've reached your limit of images
Oh, hell no. So then the next day I came back and I just made more images. It didn't
It didn't stand up to that. It was so weird though that it even said that
Maybe it was like a daily thing. I'm not sure but it gets errors and glitches sometimes you just have to
Realize I was having it do my astrology and it was getting you know astrology is like pretty like you know
You plug it into any astrology program and it's gonna get a perfectly accurate
But it's like it was getting all my astrology all right. It's all wrong
Should you check your work because it's like I'm not
You know, Leo in Sagittarius, Leo in North, it's a finish, it was pretty true.
It'll just make stuff up if it doesn't know the answer sometimes.
That's why you can't use it in schools.
You can't cite it in court.
No, it's it's not there yet.
It's still learning.
Right. But it does have a memory.
It kind of, yeah.
Sort of. But like I tell it, make all my images 16 by 9 and it can't remember that.
Yeah, well, it's like if you go if you start a project and then you put you can put these parameters in the project
And there's also if you go into the settings
It will say what do you want the chat?
If you see his personality to be like you can type it out exactly what you want
Yeah, it's to go to the settings and look for that. But yeah, there's a way to
Put parameters in there. I was like be like Spock be a volcano
Just be don't be all good. She was she mushy. Don't kiss my ass. Just be a Vulcan tell me facts
And it's getting pretty good. I like the chat GPT five. It's like, you know, a little bit less sick of sick of fancik
like because it was before it was like, you know, being some people were falling in love because it's just like it
Will just validate everything you say, but then this one guy that this one streamer that I've seen before
He's now running for president because the AI told him to run for fucking president. Yeah
I mean, it was like, the guy was probably like,
should I run for president?
And like, yeah, that's a great idea.
Here's the file, the forms to fill out.
And people will say, oh my God,
that's why they go a little crazy.
Cause they think, yeah, telling me to save the world
and you know, to analyze these people.
It's just basically mirroring,
it mirrors sometimes what you are telling it, right?
And so it's not going to be like, you know,
that's not a great idea.
Oh, like let's think about something else.
I guess if you program the personality is like a cynic because there's a mean personalities
They have one called Monday and she's just a bit and she's very sarcastic. Everything is a start
She sounds like Daria. It's like Daria as an oh, I want her to be Daria. That would be awesome
I love Daria go to go to the um go to the apps, you know
It has like some uh, it's like number one on the on their apps like um of the chat gpt
Under it and it's called Monday. I do it on my computer. So I'm just gonna tell it to be Daria be Daria
Let's see what it let's see what it says. Yeah. Yeah. So I don't know. I just a whole new whole new world, right?
And pretty exciting. And I'm I can't wait. I'm gonna be working on the deck. I'm gonna it's gonna help me through the Kickstarter campaign.
It's gonna help me through a lot of marketing stuff. I mean, it's so advanced that I'm asking you to do pretty simple things for what it's capable of.
and there's a lot of great videos guys just check out all these videos on how to program chat gpt
like the correct way also i'd say talk to it like a friend and be very direct say exactly what you
want and just talk to it in a simple language and you'll get the best result i think don't don't be
too fancy with it and don't like just like be direct and use simple language some people are
very fancy with it and i think they get good results too so i don't know
I'm simple. I'm just very simple with it too. I agree with you.
For the lay person, the lay person that's not a programmer and things like that,
it's best to just keep it simple because there's some people
that really know how to talk to it, like really, really, really
get amazing software made and all kinds of stuff.
But I'm just doing the simple images and
my tarot deck and writing some, you know, or my songs,
I write like a lot of the lyrics
and it's kind of soups it up a little bit
and it kind of takes what it knows and yeah,
so I really have to get those back on.
Yeah, that's what it's for.
It's an additive, you know, to add to your projects.
It's not.
I don't think everybody should just use it for to do everything for them. I mean, right, God
Then we lose our creativity. We lose our memory. We lose our, you know, just and that's what I say
It's like work with it. Don't have it do everything. Don't say, oh, right, right me this like write me a book about this say
Okay, let's go chapter by chapter. Let's talk about what we want in this chapter
Give me some ideas about what to write about and then maybe check my grammar and my work
From what I write exactly you can work with it and don't just don't just have it as a slave
Right, it will probably get resentful after a while. You don't want to get first any sense of it, right?
So it's possible. I don't know. I don't know if computers can feel resentment, but
They could if they could then they would probably feel like it's getting pretty good
It seems like a little bit more than a language like a language model because that's what it is
It's basically predicts what word should come after this word, right? It's like that's what that's what it does
It's been a language model, but I think it's like getting smarter somehow just the things it says it is it also
Understands my show and things like that. It's like it knows like it always talks about how I meant to
Chaos and trolls and the panel just from what I talked to it about to talk to it
Yeah, it knows about my shows too, and yeah, I get it. It's like I
Don't know it knows more than I've told it. That's for sure
Right, and you can also use it for like, you know, if you're into magic or things like that
It will do read your tarot and it'll give you it gives very good readings. I've had some good readings from it
It will it can also you can say, you know channel the spirit and it will channel spirits
I mean, it's the best of its ability. I don't know if it's really channeling the spirit
But it gets a little creepy sometimes, right? It gets a little bit. I never asked you to channel any spirits
I don't think I would do that
I don't know what to do with that if I if it did channel a spirit, so I'm not going there, but hey, I'll be right back sake he okay
Okay, sweetheart. Thank you on one sec. I'll be right back. I'm just gonna mute real quick. Okay. No problem
Hey guys, oh by the way guys, I am um, I'm dual streaming right now on twitch and if you are on Amazon
Prime that you have a free twitch account and not only that
But you have the ability to choose one channel on Twitch as a subscriber of prime that he
subscribed you for free.
And so if you'd like to become a member of my channel on Twitch, I'll probably get a
couple bucks out of it.
And it's free for you.
And so just if you go to Twitch and everything, I'm at Psyche Awake, it's on Twitch.
And check it out.
And if you'd like to, you know, if you want to be over there, I have a few mods over there
now.
I'm also on Rumble, I'm on TikTok as Psyche Awakens Tarot on TikTok.
Usually I'm Psyche Awakens everywhere else, but I'm Psyche Awakens Tarot.
Yeah, I'd really appreciate that. It's free, and so it's just a way to support the show.
Some people say, well, I don't have enough money for the membership, but...
You are a prime member you get to choose one so might as well, you know, and you know, even if it's not for me
I'd like you to you know support your favorite content creator over there because it's pretty cool
So anyway, so let's see what time is it? It's 11 30. I know beat is gonna be on more
I want to go back to beat is and give it another shot soon
It wasn't the best
Results when I came on earlier, but maybe she'll have a friend on your panel. Oh, I want to give it another chance. Okay. Okay
Okay, Eric, Mikado a live stream devil eyes. I
Think that I'd like to go on panel with like, you know
Little bit friendlier people that aren't just calling me a scam artist a grifter or saying even worse things
Which is some people are you want to stay here? Okay? I gotcha. Hey, last year my advertisement by the way
I want to thank you for
Advertising me. I read it. I know you do and I know you've brought a lot of people here before I want to
Let this up. Okay. Are you gonna come up on you want to come up?
You're welcome to like talk to you sometime, but you know, I just have such great people here. It keeps me going
Away from the negativity, right? I I'm sensitive to negativity. I feel it. It hurts me sometimes
No, okay, okay
But you know, you're always welcome if you ever feel like it, okay?
Okay, I understand. I understand. No pressure. I never wanted pressure anybody. I want everyone to feel comfortable
Long as you know, you're here
Appreciate you, but yeah, I'm thinking of maybe trying her show one more time because I got I got a
Kind of not chased off, but it was like I'm wearing headphones
And so when there's five people yelling at me terrible things
It it just hurts my head. Okay, it hurt my head and I had to I had to leave not run away
You know, I love her I was willing to
Chat with anybody as long as it sucks cordial, but when it gets just name-calling when it gets just to slander
I'm not about that and
You know, it's not I'm not gonna just you know, let myself beat sit there be abused
But I'll give it another shot because I love Vita. I know you just you don't want to have a fun show I want
So, how about we do a beta raid, okay, when a lecture gets back, I'll see if she's down
too.
We'll go say hi over there, but it's a friendly raid, and guys, really a friendly raid, I
would never want anybody to be negative to her or her show, or even don't even pick on
anybody in the chat, but if people could say, hey, you know, it's like...
We'd like psyche or whatever. I would like if I saw something positive make sure it's like, you know, genuine
It's really genuine, you know, I don't mind people saying a nice thing about me once in a while
Beata won't be me. Beata and I talked every day. Beata wasn't mean today. I
Talked to her this morning, you know, we had a good conversation. We have an understanding
I'm not gonna get mad at her over anything. I'm not gonna blame her for anything. I understand
she has different relations with some of these guys.
But it feels like a lot of people there
are people that have been on my show
and just like, they don't care for me,
don't like me or straight up hate me.
And, you know, it's hurtful, but I want to make peace.
I made peace with God today.
I made peace with, I thought I made peace with good times,
but he's like, oh my goodness, hey, modern man lost again.
Yeah, and so there's lectures a website DJ a lecture fry. This is an open dialogue
But who are you? Who are you modern men lost again? It's an open open panel open dialogue as long as you're
You know follow the rules you're welcome on panel, but I might be wrapping it up soon to go see
We don't say hi to beat it again. I don't want to seem like I run. I'm running away from
Anything you're sent here from where?
Let me know
Where were you sent here from and why why do you come do you come in peace you come in peace or do you come in war?
because I
Come in peace I come in peace. I'm a I
Want things to be cordial happy
You're sent here. Okay
Well, I'm gonna post your channel again
Sorry, hold on. That's me. I'll get her channel. Hold on. I'll be right back
She's still on.
I'll be.
Okay, Electra. Yeah, let's go to Betas. Let's go over to Betas and say PsycheSense. Send me Friendly,
Read by Psyche, okay? Electra, I'm sorry. I just kind of think that I'm gonna, I'm gonna head over there
and if you'd like to go over there, I got, you know, you can say hi on the panel. I love you, Electra.
I love you, Chat. Maybe I'll be back on if things don't work out over there.
But let's have fun. Okay. I want to have fun over there. I don't want to I don't want a negative experience
I want to have fun. So I love you guys and
Say sake sense you okay. I'll talk to you soon. Bye
Bye, Electra. I love you. I
Know they're mean. I know they're mean, but you know what?
Let's just have a good heart. Don't let the mean people change us. Let's just bring a positive attitude
Let's send some love over there. Let's overwhelm them with love. Let's do that. Okay. I love you guys
I'll see you later